Hello folks.
In this clip I'm going to teach you how to draw a jeans and t-shirt outfit for our girl here.
And I will just dive right in.
Draw her upper body and her neck just like that.
Come on down, shoulders and all the way down to her waist.
Draw her arms coming down this way.
Forearms and the fingers kind of resting on what will be her hips.
Alright, so now to draw the t-shirt.
What we're going to do is we're going to come in here and we'll just draw a little swoop just like that for the top of the t-shirt, and then just come in here and draw the sleeves like so.
You can obviously add a design to the shirt if you want to.
Not really necessary, but again, that is entirely up to you.
Come down here, we'll draw the legs. And we'll see. Since we're drawing jeans, we're going to come down all the way to the bottom here and draw the bottom of the jeans.
Come up top and draw some pockets.
Even if you want to, come in here and draw some belt loops, maybe a button.
It's up to you.
And since, I would make these jeans not completely form fitting.
I might come down here maybe add some wrinkles along the sides.
Come on down, you can add a little more depth to the bottom.
Make sure you clearly know where the knees are.
Draw some slippers on our girl.
But, yeah, there you have it.
The jeans and t-shirt look.
Fairly simple, straight forward, good, basic outfit.